0300 3020050

Select Page

Privacy
=======

At [Pseudomyxoma Survivor](https://www.pseudomyxomasurvivor.org/), we’re committed to ensuring and protecting your privacy at any time. We expect anyone involved with [Pseudomyxoma Survivor](https://www.pseudomyxomasurvivor.org/) to do the same.

Our Privacy principles
----------------------

#### 1. Introduction

This privacy notice provides you with details of how we collect and process your personal data.

[Pseudomyxoma Survivor](https://www.pseudomyxomasurvivor.org/) is the data controller and we are responsible for your personal data (referred to as “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy notice).

Our email address is [\[email protected\]](https://www.pseudomyxomasurvivor.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**.**

Our postal address is 9 Ilmington Close, Hatton Park, Warwick, CV35 7TL, UK**.**

If you are not happy with any aspect of how we collect and use your data, you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues ([_www.ico.org.uk_](http://www.ico.org.uk/)). We should be grateful if you would contact us first if you do have a complaint so that we can try to resolve it for you.

It is very important that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date. Please let us know if at any time your personal information changes by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.pseudomyxomasurvivor.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

This policy is available in paper, by request in writing.

Written by: A Brook  
Approved by: S Oliver

Review by 31 December 2024

[Home](https://www.pseudomyxomasurvivor.org/) > [Our Policies](https://www.pseudomyxomasurvivor.org/our-policies/) > Privacy

Pseudomyxoma Survivor is dedicated to supporting those affected by pseudomyxoma peritonei (PMP),  
appendix cancer and other peritoneal surface malignancies through practical and emotional support. We also raise awareness and support research.

As survivors and carers, information here is from our perspective – we are _not_ health care professionals. We are all individuals, everyone is different. We recommend that you take advice from your doctors for specific information.

Our patron is Sean Hepburn Ferrer, the son of Audrey Hepburn who passed away from appendix cancer.

Pseudomyxoma Survivor is a registered charity in England and Wales, number 1143642

Please note that we may be slower to respond to you as we would like due to volunteer availability. Thank you for your patience. [Dismiss](#)
